（忆往昔）
我的手下昨晚抓来一个离家出走的女孩
My men brought in a runaway last night.
她身上什么都没有
There's no I.D. On her … nothing on her, actually,
只有一张离开内布拉斯加的大巴票
except for a bus ticket out of Nebraska.
我叫艾莉克斯
My name is Alex.
你还活着 是因为猎人训练好了警长
You're alive because hunters trained the sheriff.
你应该说谢谢才是
I think the first words out of your mouth should be a thank you.
你们认为她是被吸血鬼抓走的吗
You think the vamps are the ones who took her?
我们以前见到过 吸血鬼把人当宠物
We've seen it before …Vampires keeping people as pets,
当血袋
human feedbags.
- 这是你家人吗 - 是
- This your family? - Yes.
他们人呢
Where are they?
克莱尔 我不是你父亲
Claire, I'm not your father.
那是你对我说的第一句话 记得吗
Those were the first words you ever said to me. Remember?
我爸爸
My dad…
他还在你身体里吗
Is he still in there?
不
No.
我在找一个人
I'm trying to track somebody down.
她叫艾米莉娅 她已经失踪多年了
Her name's Amelia. She's been missing for a few years.
她是我母亲
She's my mother.
克莱尔 你不能过去
Claire, you are not going out there.
不
No!?
妈妈
Mom!
你准备拿克莱尔怎么办
What are you gonna do about Claire?
这不取决于我
It's not up to me.
迪恩 我是乔迪·米尔斯
Hey, Dean. Jody Mills.
乔迪·米尔斯是个好人
Jody Mills is good people,
她会给你个住的地方
and she'll give you a place to crash.
让你慢慢缓过来
until you get back on your feet.
克莱尔…你如果踏上我们走的路
You know, Claire, you go down this path … our path…
干蠢事之前千万做好功课
…Do your homework before you do anything stupid, okay?
如果需要我们 我们随叫随到
And we're here if you need us, any time.
（如今）
（南达科他州 苏福尔斯）
外面冷清得都风滚草了
It's like tumbleweeds out there.
大家都哪去了
Where is everybody?
或许他们去冬季啪啪地了
Maybe they moved on to their winter humping grounds.
这里好冷啊
It's freezing.
你想离开这里吗
You want to get out of here?
不
No.
我们终于能独处了
We finally have the place to ourselves.
你是说你不喜欢
You mean you don't like it.
旁边的车
when the, uh, car next to you's.
上下晃动 还发出呻吟声吗
bumping up and down and you hear groaning?
没人能听到我们吧
Nobody can hear us, can they?
今晚不会的
Not tonight.
道格
Doug!
你在做什么
What the hell are you doing?!
他知道
He knows.
是吧
Don't you?
我发誓我什么都不知道
I swear I don't know anything.
求你
Please.
你是什么
What are you?
What are you?!
[邪恶力量 第11季第12集]
你给我们找到案子了吗
Did you catch us a case?
没有
Um, no.
听啊
Get this.
有人拍了张照片
Some… some dude took a picture.
一只鼬鼠骑着一只飞行的啄木鸟
of a weasel riding a flying woodpecker.
飞在半空中 真是疯狂
Midair. I-it's kind of nuts.
那么阿玛拉也没有消息喽
So, I'm guessing there's nothing on the mar-meter, either.
是啊
No.
我开始觉得上帝的疯子妹妹
I'm starting to think that God's psycho sister.
可能转入地下了
has gone to ground.
你呢 小卡有消息吗
What about you? Hear from cas?
没有 他说他在想办法引她出洞
No, he said he was working on something to draw her out,
但他离开后就一直没消息了
but it's been radio silence since he was here.
嗯 这么安静让我好不舒服
Yeah, all this quiet's starting to wig me out.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
那是 猫王
That? That's the Elvis.
猫王
Elvis?
那是…
Is that a…
- 糖衣甜甜圈 - 嗯
- That's a glazed doughnut. - Yeah.
其实是两个
Two, actually.
上面一个 下面一个
One topside, one on the bottom.
比较差劲的那种
Now, your inferior versions…
只用一个甜甜圈 从中间切开
they'll just take one doughnut, split it right down the middle.
这才是好货
Boom.
好吧 希望你吃得愉快
All right, well, uh, hope you enjoy it.
这世上还有孩子吃不饱呢
You know there are starving children out there.
哥们 我身经百战 没死在妖魔鬼怪手里
Dude, I'm not gonna survive hundreds of monster attacks.
也不要死在双甜甜圈怪手里
to get flatlined by… by some double doughnut monstrosity.
这是猫王
The Elvis!
随你说吧
Whatever it…
这东西有多少卡路里啊
How many calories are in that thing?
好久不见
Long time.
你的《疯狂高尔夫》影评早该出来了
Your, uh, "Caddyshack" review is way overdue.
嗯 没问题 我们就去
Yeah, you got it. We're there.
想去趟南达科他州吗
How do you feel about South Dakota?
据传
Word on the street.
我现在站在王室旁边
is that I'm in the presence of royalty…
你们会当选舞会国王和王后
Future prom king and queen.
你们现在领先
You guys are in the lead.
不会吧
No way.
亨利 对你来说当然可能 但我怎么可能
No, I mean, yeah, for you, Henry, but not me.
另外 这个还有人在做吗
Also, people still do that?
我以为这都是80年代的事了
I thought it was, like, an '80s thing.
是啊 还有王冠什么的呢
Oh, yeah, there's crowns and everything.
得啦 我们好好享受一番
Come on. Let's have fun with it.
我穿裙子 你穿西装
I'll wear the dress. You wear the tux.
你的胸可撑不起我的裙子
You don't have the boobs for my dress.
什么 拜托 看我这对儿胸器
What? Come on. Look at those things.
P老师
Hey, Mr. P.
艾莉克斯 明天的测试准备好了吗
Alex, you ready for the test tomorrow?
没有
So not.
那幸好你还有18小时做准备
Oh, lucky you've got 18 hours to prep.
祝你愉快
Good times.
- 回见 - 回见
- See ya. - See ya.
天呐 化学实验课上
Oh, my God. Chem lab…
我在自己的口水里睡着了
I fell asleep in a pool of my own drool.
教练说明天有两节的训练
Oh, and coach is calling double practice tomorrow.
中场需要好好练习
Midfield needs serious tightening.
怎么了
What?
就是
Just…
你的表现好棒啊
You're killing it out there.
得了
Shut up.
融入得很好
Fitting right in.
温家兄弟
The Winchesters?
他们怎么来了
Why would they be here?
我又没亮蝙蝠灯
I didn't put up the bat signal.
这下邻里不得安宁了
Well, there goes the neighborhood.
- 我帮帮你吧 - 谢谢
- Let me help you out. - Oh, thank you.
- 不客气 - 过来
- Yeah, sure. - Come here.
太久没见了
It has been too long.
嗯 是啊 真是太久了
Yeah, clearly, it's been too long.
艾莉克斯 是你吧
'cause, Alex, that is you, right?
我没变化那么大吧
I don't look that different.
每天早上在浴室里
It's amazing what you can accomplish.
待两小时 成效惊人
when you spend two hours in the bathroom every morning.
你什么时候还早起了
Since when are you even up in the morning?
你现在居然醒着都是奇迹
I'm surprised you're awake now.
他们俩赶来肯定不是为了
Hey, I'm pretty sure the guys didn't come here.
看你们互相厮杀
to watch you two kill each other.
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
我不是不小心臀播了你们的电话吧
I didn't accidentally butt-dial you or anything, did I?
是我找了他们 是关于
I called about the monsters.
你不肯相信是怪物的怪物
that you refuse to believe are monsters.
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding.
如果你们问过我
You know, if you'd checked in with me,
就能省了跑这趟了
I could have saved you a trip.
我们想着反正也该来看看你了
Well, we figured we owed you the visit.
其实 我正需要帮手
And you know what? Actually, I could use the backup.
给我吧
Let me have that.
我再去烤一只鸡
I'm gonna go put another chicken on.
你们坐舒服点
You settle in.
还是再烤两只吧 我…
M-might want to make it two. I'm…Just gonna…
- 嗯 - 我饿死了
- Yeah. - I'm starving.
这鸡肉太好吃了
Oh, this bird is fantastic.
再搭配土豆和豆子
And when you mix it up with the potatoes and the… the beans…
你们每天都这么吃吗
You guys eat like this every day?
就是鸡肉而已啊
It's just chicken.
而且有鸡的样子
It's shaped like chicken.
不是肉饼或者鸡块
Not a patty or… or a nugget.
能不能说案子了
Can we get to the case?
有三个人失踪了
Three people are missing.
没有证据表明他们不是自己离镇了
There is no evidence that they didn't skip town on their own.
两个是离家出走少年 一个流浪汉
Two of them were runaways. One was a homeless guy.
最后有人见到他是在布雷登口
He was last seen at Brayden Point.
我一直在盯梢那里
I've been stalking it out.
嗯
Right.
哥们
Dude.
还有很多呢 布雷登口
There's plenty left. Brayden Point?
是的 孩子们去那儿亲热
Yeah, it's where the kids go to make out.
是的 炉子上还剩四磅左右的呢
And, yes, there's about four pounds left on the stove.
两位 外面有鬼怪
Guys, there's something out there.
有人说见到了他们从未见过的动物
People are reporting animals they've never seen before,
有东西在他们前院逗留随后又消失
things stalking their front yards that disappear.
这是…放回去
This is according to the… hey, put it back…
克莱尔在追的邻里犯罪博客上写的
Neighborhood crime blogs that Claire has been reading.
那是目击者证词
They're eyewitness accounts.
我们还办过证据更少的案子呢
We've hunted on less.
还有什么
What else you got?
我还在查
I'm… I'm working on it.
克莱尔抓到过一个狼人
Claire did catch a werewolf.
对了 其实是一只有狂犬病的德国牧羊犬
Oh, right, it turned out to be a German shepherd with rabies.
在那之前是吸血鬼
And before that was the vampire…
喜欢色情cos的议员女士
councilwoman into erotic cosplay.
那之前我都不知道cos是啥
I didn't know what cosplay was before that.
警队丢尽了脸
Super-embarrassing for the whole force.
你没闲着啊
You've been busy.
我一直在猎魔
I've been hunting.
也就是骚扰无辜之人
A.K.A., menacing innocent people.
克莱尔积攒了一堆袭人案底
Claire has a whole string of assaults racked up.
她现在没进监狱的唯一原因
The only reason she's not sitting in jail right now.
是我是治安官
is that I'm the sheriff.
好吧 我出过错
Fine, I've been wrong.
但这次肯定是有怪物
But this time I know there's a monster.
我们能不能不说什么怪物 猎魔了
Can we stop talking about monsters and hunting?
现实生活呢
What about real life?
现实生活
Real life?
好啊
Okay.
好啊 我们说实在的吧
Yeah, sure. Let's get real.
你和亨利选好周末了吗
You and Henry settle on a weekend yet?
什么
What?
你们打算什么时候溜去乔迪的小屋
When you're sneaking out to Jody's cabin.
乱搞啊
to screw yourselves silly.
开始了
Here we go.
我们才没…
We're not…
你就是个疯子
You're completely insane.
你最好先清空你的谷歌聊天再跟他搞吧
You might want to clear your g-chats before you commit to that.
这似乎是家务事
This seems like, uh, family business.
给我坐着
Sit! Stay!
艾莉克斯 你有什么想说的吗
Alex, anything you want to say?
没有
Nope.
好吧 我可能…
Okay, uh, well, um, I-I may have…
我看到你背包里的避孕药了
I've definitely seen birth control pills in your backpack.
- 要说这个了啊 - 好吧
- Oh, we're going there. - Okay.
天呐
Oh, my God.
如果这事不能说 那就更不该做了 是吧
Hey, if we can't talk about it, we shouldn't be doing it, right?
是吧
Right?
什么
What?
好吧 我不会说
Okay, I'm not gonna tell you.
你太小还不能做爱 对你也是
that you are too young to be having sex, or you.
她要跟谁做爱啊
Who's she gonna have sex with?
她都不跟任何人说话
She doesn't talk to anybody.
但我要说
What I will tell you.
避孕药是无法防止性病传播的
is that birth control pills are useless against STDs.
不管你跟谁做 每次都要戴套
Whoever you are with needs to suit up every time, always.
不能提早拉起吊桥
No pulling up the drawbridge early.
明白啦
Oh, I get it.
而且别指望男人 不管我多喜欢亨利
And don't expect the guy, as much as I love Henry,
总会带着套套来
to always show up packing.
是吧
Am I right?
什么
What?
不是吧
Seriously?
别说了 我们还什么都没做呢
Stop! We haven't done anything yet.
我只是 想备着点
I'm just… trying to be prepared.
那好
Great.
我们还需要土豆泥 是吧
We need some more mashed potatoes, right?
土豆泥 我去…
Mashed pota… I'm just gonna… I'm gonna…
我去再拿点土豆泥来
I'm gonna get some more potatoes.
土豆…
Po-ta-toes.
这真好玩
This is fun.
好个埋伏啊
Nice ambush in there.
是你们不告而来在先
Hey, you guys crashed my pad first.
你得知道 有怪物我们帮忙
Well, you know, thought we were gonna be helping you.
避孕你得自己教
with monsters, not birth control.
这就是我的世界
Welcome to my world.
别误会 我很爱她们
I mean, don't get me wrong, I love those girls,
但我真是在勉强支撑
but, man, I am hanging on by my fingertips.
上个被克莱尔当成怪物的人
The last guy Claire pegged as a monster,
她拿剑架在了他脖子上
she held a sword to his throat.
他一心想提出指控
He is hell-bent on pressing charges.
老实说
You know, I got to be honest,
我以为是艾莉克斯会适应不来呢
I thought it was gonna be Alex with the, uh, adjustment issues.
是啊 她也有过艰难时期
Oh, yeah, it was rough going there for a bit, too.
但今年一切都顺利起来了
But this year, everything clicked.
她还跟学校里最受欢迎的男生约会呢
She's dating the most popular guy in school, for gosh sake.
是啊 我都要认不出她了
Yeah, I know. I barely recognized her.
就算这样 我觉得我该教她
But even there, I feel like I should be teaching her.
男友和恋爱的一些东西
about boyfriends and relationships.
就是一个妈妈该教女儿的东西
You know, stuff a mom would teach her.
萨姆和我当年如果有人教就好了
Sammy and I could have benefited from a little of that.
是啊 但我不是艾莉克斯的妈妈
Yeah, but I'm not Alex's mom.
我也不是克莱尔的妈妈 我没有养大她们
I'm not Claire's mom. I didn't raise them.
我跟她们没有那样的过去
I don't have that kind of history with them.
我们会跟克莱尔谈的 让她安顿下来
We can talk to Claire, and we'll get her to settle down.
克莱尔的问题不止是打人
It's not just Claire busting heads.
还有吗
There's more?
她开始上大学了
Yeah, she started college,
但她好几周没去上课
but she hasn't been to classes for weeks.
也没有朋友
She doesn't have any friends.
她成天去找案子 阅读传说
She spends all her time trolling for cases and reading lore.
你这么一说感觉好恐怖
Sounds kind of creepy when you put it like that.
我并不反对猎魔
You know, I've got nothing against hunting,
但如果她是借此逃避
but if she's hiding in it.
因为她没有别的可做 那我就…
because she doesn't have anything else, I'm just…
她那么独来独往我很担心
I'm worried about her being so alone.
我会让萨姆去开导她
Well, I'll put Sammy on it.
反正他更擅长跟人谈心
He's better with the whole talky thing, anyway.
- 谢啦 - 嗯
- Thanks. - Yeah.
请进
Come in.
克莱尔
Claire.
有时间吗
You, uh… you got a minute?
嗯
Yeah.
看来你我在装潢方面意见一致
Looks like you and I have the same decorating philosophy.
我又不需要往墙上贴贾斯汀·比伯
It's not like I need the Biebs on my wall.
我想明天我们可以去找
I was thinking tomorrow we could go to the families.
那些失踪者的家人
of the people who disappeared.
看看他们之间是否有联系
and, like, see if there's any connection between them.
嗯
Right, um…
关于那事 克莱尔
About that, Claire…
我了解这种事
I know how it can be.
猎魔会吞噬你的生活 而不是朝九晚五
The hunter life consumes you. There's no 9:00-to-5:00.
你对一切都草木皆兵
You start seeing monsters at every quik mart in town.
你觉得我是疯了吗
So you think I'm nuts?
不是的
No, of course not.
我的意思是 我并不确定真有案子
What I'm saying is I'm not sure you have a case.
而最近 你似乎一直在找
And lately, it seems like you've spent a lot of time.
并不存在的怪物
hunting monsters that weren't there.
那是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你不会是第一个
You wouldn't be the first hunter.
想逃避的猎人
who was trying to escape something.
那我在逃避什么呢
And what am I escaping, exactly,
除了令人麻痹的无聊
aside from mind-numbing boredom?
你说呢
You tell me.
跟乔迪和艾莉克斯处得如何
I mean, how are things with Jody and Alex?
我并没有在选边站
And I'm not taking sides.
我只是想理解现在的情况
I'm just trying to understand what's going on.
她们并不是有意让我难过
They're not trying to make me feel bad.
艾莉克斯倒是 她讨厌我
I mean, Alex is. She hates me.
但是
But, um…
有时我就是觉得
sometimes I just feel like.
我加入乔迪和艾莉克斯太晚了
I'm a little late to the Jody and Alex show.
嗯
Yeah.
她们一起经历了一些很艰辛的事
Well, they have been through some heavy crap together.
或许我该自己出去闯了
Maybe it's time I just head out on my own.
做个全职猎人
and be a full-fledged hunter.
克莱尔 我能理解想猎魔的心理
Claire, I absolutely understand the need to hunt.
我真的理解
Believe me, I do.
但怪物是不会被消灭干净的
But the monsters are always going to be there,
永远没有穷尽
on and on, forever.
但组建家庭 上学的机会
But a chance at a family, a home, school…
过了可能就没有了
that won't be.
快走 我们要迟到了
Come on. We're gonna be late.
我想在测试之前跟P老师谈谈
I want to catch Mr. P. before the test.
被害人是史蒂芬·菲尔普斯
Victim's name is Stephen Phelps.
数学老师
He was a math teacher.
艾莉克斯最喜欢的老师了
Alex's favorite, actually.
很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
菲尔普斯被倒挂在
Phelps was found hanging upside-down.
旗杆顶端 用胶带绑在了上面
from the top of the flagpole, duct-taped…
脖子似乎先被人折断了
Like his neck had been snapped first.
有目击者吗
Any witnesses?
只有有幸发现了他的管理员
Only the lucky custodian that found him.
凶手怎么把菲尔普斯弄上去的
So, how did the killer get Phelps up there in the first place?
除非他自己有消防车
Unless he had his own fire truck?
是啊 难道凶手背着个男人
Yeah, so our killer climbs up 20 feet.
爬了20英尺 然后用胶带把他绑在了上面吗
with a guy on his back and then duct-tapes him?
是啊 而且为什么
Yeah, and why?
我们在旗杆旁发现了这个 不知有没有什么用
We found this around the flagpole if it means anything.
已经把样本送去实验室了
We already sent a sample to the lab.
你对菲尔普斯还有什么了解
What else do you know about Phelps?
只知道他是个好老师
Just that he was a damn fine teacher.
他真的帮了艾莉克斯很多 这我知道
He really helped Alex out. I know that.
我就知道 到底是什么
I knew it. So, what are we dealing with?
- 恶魔 鬼魂附体 - 克莱尔
- Demons? Ghost possession? - Claire,
这是犯罪现场 你不能进来
this is a crime scene. You can't be here.
那假联调局就行吗
Oh, but the fake FBI can?
小点声
Keep your voice down!
过来 过来
Come here. Come here.
我是想办案
I was trying to work the case…
人人都说不存在的案子
the case everyone said wasn't real.
告诉你 你说对了
And you know what? You were right, okay?
这里面是有点鬼
There is something unnatural going on here,
但你不能走到一群警官面前
but you can't just walk up in front of a bunch of officers.
要求治安官向你透露
and demand that the sheriff give you details.
凶案调查的细节
on a murder investigation.
我们能不能谈尸体的问题了
Can we talk about the body now?
我还没说完呢
Oh, I'm not even near finished.
你得对乔迪放尊重点
You need to show Jody a little respect.
她接纳你是帮了大忙
She did you a huge solid by taking you in.
她帮你找了学校
She got you set up at school.
我不想上学
I don't want to go to school.
没人喜欢上学 克莱尔
Nobody wants to go to school, Claire.
- 那可是学校啊 - 就是嘛
- It's school. - Exactly.
我的意思是 她为了让你
My point is she's been busting her ass.
过上正常生活忙里忙外
to get you set up with a life.
她给你饭吃
She's feeding you.
你的房间现在比我的还好
Hell, you got a nicer room than I do now.
她让你不用蹲监狱
She kept you out of jail.
我又没让她那么做
I never asked her to.
我就是想说这个
And that's what I'm talking about.
你得有点感恩的样子
You need to act like you give a crap.
你得知道感激她为你做的…
You need to appreciate what that woman's do…
学校停课了
They canceled school.
我们就去…别处了
So we're gonna… hang out, I guess.
去别处啊
Hang out, huh?
嗯 那好了
Yeah. Okay, then.
嗯 他肯定明白了
Oh, yeah. He got the message.
当然了
Damn right he did.
当然
I'm sure.
你去哪…
Where you go…
怎么都走了呢
People walking away from me!
你还认识联调局的人
You know the FBI?
是乔迪认识
Jody does.
菲尔普斯老师最近跟谁闹过矛盾吗
Was there anyone that Mr. Phelps had run-ins with recently…
教职工 家长 学生
Staff, parents, students?
据我所知是没有
No, not that I know of.
家长还给他烤巧克力蛋糕呢
Parents would bake brownies for that man.
好吧 我们需要找
Oh, okay, well, we're gonna want to, um,
教职工和学生谈话
interview staff and students,
还需要人事档案
as well as have access to personnel records.
尽管说
Whatever you need.
我们一定要抓到那混蛋
We got to catch that bastard…
把他里子翻出来 吊起来
turn his insides out and string him up.
很高兴你这么支持我们
Glad you're on our side.
我早上去升旗
Well, I raise the flag in the morning.
就看到他被绑在上面
and, uh, he's… he's s-stuck up there,
像只棍子上的虫子
you know, like a bug on a stick.
我一开始还以为是恶作剧
I thought it was a prank at first,
是绑了个假人什么的
but, uh, you know, like it was a dummy or something like that,
结果并不是
but, uh it wasn't.
你认识菲尔普斯老师吗
Did you know Mr. Phelps?
见过他
Seen him around.
学校最近有发生什么
Have you noticed anything weird or out of the ordinary.
奇怪 不寻常的事吗
going on at the school lately?
你是指比老师被杀
You mean weirder than a dead teacher.
用胶带绑在旗杆上还怪的吗
taped to the top of a flagpole or…?
你发现菲尔普斯老师之前
Before you discovered Mr. Phelps,
有察觉任何奇怪的景象 声音或气味吗
had you noticed any unusual sights or sounds or smells?
气味
Smells.
这里一直臭臭的
Uh, I mean, you know, this place kind of always stinks.
孩子可邋遢了
The kids are slobs, you know?
但我只能尽力
But I do the best that I can, but, uh…
维勒先生 你今早见到了
Mr. Weiler, you don't seem too upset.
那样恐怖的景象 可你似乎没怎么受影响
about the, uh, graphic scene you came upon this morning.
我能说什么呢
Well, I mean, what can I tell you?
我又不认识他
I mean, I-I didn't know the guy.
你发现尸体前 从昨晚到今早
And where were you last night, and earlier this morning,
都在哪
before you found the body?
这不会外传的吧
This is confidential, right?
我在瞎驴子醉得不省人事
I was passed out at the Blind Donkey.
这里比看上去大得多啊
This place is bigger than it looks.
每间教室 办公室
Checked every classroom, every office,
走廊 厕所都查了
every hallway, and every bathroom,
冲那厕所真该拿危险工作补贴
and I deserve hazard pay for that.
- 有发现吗 - 没有
- And? - Nothing.
没有电磁干扰 没有巫术袋 没有硫磺
No EMF, no hex bags, no sulfur.
只发现几个老师
The only thing I found were a couple of teachers.
在休息室里亲热
making out in the break room.
那你的发现也比我多 一个目击者都没有
Well, you got more than I did. Not one witness.
但那个管理员
Oh, but the custodian…
他绝对有点问题
there's definitely something up with him.
他…古古怪怪的
He's…squirrelly.
年度最佳老师被贴在旗杆上
Well, teacher of the year gets run up a flagpole,
却没人了解情况
and nobody knows squat?
肯定有古怪
Something's going on here.
你没事吧
You okay?
我知道你跟菲尔普斯老师关系很好
I know you were tight with Mr. Phelps.
他觉得我很聪明
He thought I was super-smart.
他劝我放弃足球 加入数学队
Said I should ditch soccer and join the math team.
你的确很聪明
You are super-smart.
他肯定遭了很大的罪
What he must have gone through…
没人该死得那么惨
Nobody should die like that.
有人就是那么变态
People are messed up.
没想到苏福尔斯附近还真会
Never thought we'd have an actual psychopath.
有这样的疯子
here in Sioux Falls.
这世上有很多可怕的东西
There are awful things out there.
什么意思
What do you mean?
亨利
Henry…
我并不一直是现在这样
I wasn't always this girl.
有时候我照着镜子
Sometimes I look at myself in the mirror,
会想 「那是我吗」
and I'm like, "That's me?"
嗯 你说过 你不得不逃家
Yeah, you said you had to run away from home?
乔迪收留了你
Jody took you in?
你得知道
You should know…
我以前做过很坏的事
I've done some really bad things.
放我出去
Let me out!
伤过人
Hurt people.
你知道我要对你做什么吗
You got any idea what I'm about to do to you?
我知道
Yeah. I do.
什么都做不了
Nothing.
怎么回事
What the…?
我早该告诉你的
I should have told you before.
人人都做过自己不耻的事
Everybody's done stuff they're ashamed of.
我们中学时
I mean there was this one kid.
欺负过一个孩子
we all tortured in middle school.
我都不愿去想
I-I can't even think about it.
艾莉克斯
Alex, hey.
我不在乎
I don't care.
不管你做了什么 我都不在乎 好吗
Whatever it is you did, I don't, okay?
如果你不想 也不用告诉我
And you never have to tell me anything if you don't want to.
犯罪现场的纤维检验结果出来了
Got the results back on that fiber from the crime scene.
- 是什么 - 石棉
- And? - Asbestos.
- 石棉 - 嗯
- Asbestos? - Yeah.
怎么 凶手防火吗
So our killer's fire-retardant?
这意味着什么
What does that mean?
现在还猜不出
Well, not much yet.
还有 守卫维勒 他的不在场证明没问题
And Weiler the janitor… his alibi checks out.
但他的社保号码不对
Well, his social security number does not.
那原属于1988年死去的梅米·加西亚
It belongs to Mamie Garcia, who died in 1988.
维勒几个月前才入职
And Weiler started at Marshall a few months ago,
失踪案就是那时开始的
when the disappearances started…
就是我早说有问题的那些失踪案
the ones I said were supernatural in the first place.
嗯 我们知道 你一直在提这茬
Yes, we know. You keep reminding us.
那么我们需要再跟这位维勒先生谈谈了
So we need to talk to this Mr. Weiler again.
好吧 我在数据库里查下他的照片
Okay, I'm gonna run his I.D. photo through the database.
我也一起去
I'm coming with you.
我有套联调局西装 我可以扮成新学员
I have a Fed suit, and I can be your new agent trainee.
稍等一下 匡提科
Okay, hold on there, Quantico.
你和我半小时后还有事
You and I are leaving in a half an hour.
去登记 记得吗
The registrar… remember?
改天再去吧
Reschedule it.
又改期
Again?
你今晚得去求他让你重新入学
You are going to beg him to let you re-enroll tonight.
还有个凶手在逍遥法外呢
When there's a killer out there?
我觉得好傻啊
I feel like a total asshat.
谁会穿成这样
Who dresses like this?
杀人犯去见法官时穿礼服
You know, there is a reason why murderers put on monkey suits.
是有原因的
when they go in front of a judge.
乔迪
Jody!
我一直觉得你是比较漂亮的那个
I always thought you were the pretty one.
假地址
And a fake address.
我爱死这哥们了
Oh, I'm loving this guy.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
迪恩 赶快…
Dean, you need…
乔迪
Jody?
不 不
Oh, no! No!
乔迪
Jody?
克莱尔
Claire?
我去检查房内
I'll check the house.
该死
Damn it!
没有 没人
Nothing. No one.
- 这是克莱尔的刀子 - 对
- It's Claire's knife. - Yeah.
不管是什么 它趁她们离开时埋伏了进来
So whatever it was, it was lying in wait for them when they left.
我是努恩探员
This is Agent Noon.
我也没看到治安官
No, I have not seen the sheriff, either.
我很愿意转达给她
I'd be happy to pass on the information.
我正跟我搭档在一起 你有什么情况
I'm just here with my partner. Uh, what do you got?
他们确定了管理员的身份
They identified the custodian.
好
Okay.
理查德·毕桑
Richard Beesom.
内布拉斯加州奥尼尔市的一个卡车司机
He's a trucker out of O'Neill, Nebraska.
他已经失踪三年了
He's been missing for three years.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他的家人被发现失血而死
His family was found exsanguinated…
喉咙被撕裂
throats ripped out.
- 他是吸血鬼 - 对
- He's a vampire? - Yeah.
奥尼尔 那不是艾莉克斯的家乡吗
O'Neill… isn't that where Alex was from?
当年她的巢穴所在
Where her nest was?
那么毕桑是艾莉克斯之前巢穴的人
So, what, Beesom was part of Alex's old nest?
是来找艾莉克斯的
Came here looking for Alex.
结果却撞见了乔迪和克莱尔
and then found Jody and Claire instead?
我不知道 还是有哪里不对劲
I don't know. Something still doesn't sit right.
我们得去提醒艾莉克斯
We got to warn Alex.
嗯 你去接她
Yeah, all right, you pick her up.
我去查一下毕桑的办公室
I'll go check Beesom's office.
那里肯定有线索
There's bound to be something there.
你在哪 我去接你
Hey, where are you? I'm coming to get you.
我在湖街的50代餐馆
I'm at 50's on lake.
好 乖乖等我过去
Okay, sit tight till I get there.
- 千万不要一个人乱走 - 怎么了
- Do not go off by yourself. - What's going on?
你们学校的管理员是个吸血鬼
The custodian at your school… he's a vamp.
天哪 不是吧
Oh, my God. No.
听我说 我五分钟内赶到
Listen to me. I'll be there in five minutes.
别乱动 明白吗
Don't move. You understand?
好
Yeah.
谁啊
Who was that?
你得走了
You need to go.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你得马上离开我
You need to get away from me now.
把我留这儿就行
Just leave me here.
我不能放你走
I can't let you go.
不是吧
Oh, come on!
艾莉克斯不见了
Alex is gone.
迪恩 我刚刚找到一张学校的旧地图
Dean, listen, I just found an old school map.
有栋建筑原本是个游泳池
Uh, there's a building that used to be the pool.
因为石棉问题而被校方关闭
They closed it down because it had asbestos.
毕桑肯定是把她们带去那里了
That has to be where Beesom took them.
我距离那里就15分钟车程
I'm 15 minutes away.
好 是在学校最东面 蒙罗对面
All right, uh, it's at the east end of the school across Menlo.
我也这就赶过去
I'm heading there now.
这就是那些失踪者的尸体
Those are the bodies that went missing.
只是点外卖而已
Just a little take-out.
等着收垃圾日呢
Waiting for trash day.
你是对的
You were right.
为什么带我们来这里
What are we here for?
不
No.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is this?
你的整个人生
Your whole life.
家人重聚感觉怎么样
How's this for a family reunion, huh?
本来也该邀请我家人的 不过
Would have invited my own, but, uh,
他们几年前死了
they died a couple years ago.
你知道怎么死的吗
Do you know how?
你认出我是谁了吗
You figured out who I am?
我不认识你
I don't know you.
你不记得了
You don't remember?
你夺走了我的生命 现在居然不记得了
Well, you took my life, and you don't remember?
三年前 内布拉斯加
Three years ago. Nebraska.
在一个酒吧外 有个人渣想带你回家
Some sleazebag was taking you home outside of a bar,
我把他赶跑了
and I chased him off.
因为你是那么年轻
'cause, see, you were so young,
我能看出你一点都不想跟那个人走
and I could see you didn't want anything to do with the guy.
我以为是有皮条客逼你卖淫呢
I mean, I- I- I thought maybe some pimp was working you.
我给了你几张二十美元 说会送你回家
I gave you a few $20s and told you I would drive you home.
我记得你
I do remember you.
太好了
Oh, good.
你记得当时一路上你一言未发吗
You remember how you didn't say a word all the way there?
这是你家吗
Is this your house?
然后他们来了
And then they came.
怎么…
What…?
放开我
Get off me!
一群饥渴的吸血鬼猛扑向我
The whole starving pack tore into me.
他们生生吸干了我
They drank me alive.
他们转化了我
They turned me!
别碰她 她当时别无选择
Leave her alone! She had no choice!
这时真正好玩的故事上演了
That is when the real fun began.
因为当我回到家想把这件事告诉我妻子时
because I went home to tell my wife what happened,
当时我全身都沾满了自己的鲜血
but, see, I was covered in blood… my own blood,
这让我变得疯狂 饥渴无比
which made me crazy, starving.
我失去了控制
I lost control.
我将她开肠破肚 还有我儿子
I gutted her…And my boy.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
是他们逼我的
They… they made me.
你完全可以让我留在酒吧外
You could have left me outside that bar.
我当时是想帮你的
I tried to help you!
我是个好人
I was a good man!
唯一能让我支撑下去的动力
And, you know, the only thing that kept me going.
就是我知道总有一天我会找到你
was the knowledge that I would find you one day,
让你血债血偿
and I would make you pay.
理查跟踪你好几个月了 艾莉克斯
You see, Rich was tracking you for months, Alex.
他一直在监视你
Yeah, he's… he's been watching you.
为什么
What for?
我本来是想直接把你杀了
Well, I was just gonna kill you outright,
但你当时那么可怜 孤单一人
but, of course, you just were so miserable and alone.
杀了你岂不是便宜了你
it would have been a mercy killing, right?
我想先让你觉得幸福
I wanted you to be happy first.
让你拥有珍视之物
I wanted you to have something precious.
然后再从你身边夺走它
so that I could take it from you.
所以他转化了学校最受欢迎的男孩子
So…He turned the most popular kid in school.
让我来找你 我先让你快乐起来
and sent me after you… I'd build you up…
然后我就一步步击溃你
Then I'd chop you right down piece by piece.
我要夺走你的老师
I'd take your teacher…
你的恋人 你的家人
Your boyfriend, your family,
然后把你喂给我巢穴的人
and then I'll feed you to my nest.
一切都是骗我的吗
Nothing? None of it was real?
说真的 艾莉
Seriously, Al?
你就是个怪胎
You were a complete freak.
你怒气冲冲地在学校里独来独往
I mean, you were an angry loner creeping around the school.
穿着风衣 像个黑手党似的
like some kind of trench coat mafia.
等着下地狱吧 你这变态
You're gonna burn in hell, you sociopath.
我可不跟你这样的姑娘约会
I could never date someone like you.
住手
Stop it!
这事你不许掺和
Don't mess with this one.
亨利脾气还挺坏的
Henry's got a real mean streak, you know?
他不肯简单杀了菲尔普斯老师
You know, this one couldn't just kill Mr. Phelps.
还非要把他挂在旗杆上供全校师生瞻仰
He had to run him up a flagpole for the whole school to salute.
她看见他了是吧
Well, she saw him, didn't she?
你引来了不少警察
You brought a lot of cops.
但亨利还年轻 他会吸取教训
But Henry's young. He'll learn.
放手
Get off me!
- 他们知道我们在这儿 - 不
- They know we're here! - No!
那些联调局的 他们是猎人
Those FBI… they're hunters!
他们知道你们杀了菲尔普斯
They know that you killed Phelps.
是他们杀了艾莉克斯巢穴的人 问她
And they killed Alex's entire nest! Just ask her!
是真的 他们马上就来了
It's… it's true. They're coming for you.
闭嘴
Shut up!
亨利 杀戮和逃亡
Henry, the killing and running all the time.
不是你想要的
you don't want that.
是你造成的 你给我们带来了这一切
You did this! You did this to all of us!
看着你爱的人一个个死去吧
You are gonna watch everyone you love die.
你情报有误 死猪头 艾莉克斯讨厌我
Check your Intel, you pig! Alex hates me.
我会帮你
I- I- I'll help you.
放过他们 我可以做你的诱饵
Let them go, and I'll lure for you.
你知道我很擅长
You know how good I am.
我帮整个巢穴存活了八年
I kept a whole nest alive for eight years.
没有猎物时 你们可以喝我的血
And… and you can feed on me when the hunting goes dry.
总会有狩猎无果的时候
And it goes dry. I know.
这事我会考虑的
You know, I might take you up on that.
不
No!
萨姆
Sam!
不
No!
克莱尔
Claire.
没人会来救你
No one's gonna save you.
- 你喝他们的血了吗 - 没有
- Did you drink their blood? - No.
迪恩
Dean.
乔迪
Jody.
肯定是我的腿
It had to be the leg.
- 我需要拄拐了 - 我帮你
- I'm gonna need bionics. - Come here.
他随你处置
He's all yours now.
早知道就抓住机会和你啪啪了
I should have tapped that when I had the chance.
做你的春梦去吧
Keep dreaming about me.
果然是培根烤糊的味儿
Yeah, I thought I smelled burning bacon.
是你们俩做的吗
You two cooked?
我们努力了
Uh, we tried.
薄煎饼可能有点生
The pancakes might be a little raw.
我们想为你做点事
We wanted to do something for you.
好了 别这么看我
Okay, stop looking at me like that.
我感觉自己像小蒂姆（出自狄更斯《圣诞颂歌》）
I feel like tiny Tim.
很抱歉他伤害了你们俩
I'm sorry he hurt you… both of you.
我们没事
Hey, we're fine.
我们三个都完好无损 没关系的
We're in three whole pieces, more or less. It's okay.
有关系
It's not okay.
他差点因为我做的事 杀死你们
He almost killed you for what I did.
是那些吸血鬼干的 你那时只是个孩子
It's for what those vamps did. You were a kid.
你只能按他们说的做
You had to do whatever they said.
艾莉克斯
Alex…
你甘愿为我们放弃生命
…You were ready to give up your life for us.
你很善良了
That's goodness.
这就是家庭的可怕之处
And that's what's scary about family.
让你有很多害怕失去的东西
It gives you so much to lose.
你不必担心
You don't have to worry.
我知道我拥有什么
I know what I have.
你真该看到乔迪解决那个吸血鬼的样子
You should have seen Jody take out that vamp.
她愿意为我挡子弹
She would have taken a bullet for me.
那么你会不给她找那么多麻烦了吗
Does that mean you're gonna make her life less hellish?
我郑重发誓不会像傻瓜一样猎魔
I solemnly swear not to hunt like a dumbass.
乔迪说她会教我搜寻线索
Jody said that she's gonna teach me to vet leads.
教我如何调查
and teach me how to investigate.
她觉得我会把自己害死
She think I'm gonna get myself killed.
你没事吧
You all right?
嗯 谢了
Yeah. Ahh, thanks.
老兄 我拿了肋排 两桶沙司
Dude, we got ribs and, uh, two tubs of sauce.
你不许吃我的
'cause you're not touching mine.
- 好诶 - 昨晚做的晚饭 但没能吃上
- Yes. - Made them for dinner last night, but didn't get to eat it,
因为被绑架了什么的
what with the multiple kidnappings and all.
- 是啊 - 是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
等下
One second.
你会没事吧
Are you gonna be all right?
嗯 周一上学去
Yeah. School on Monday.
你要去参加生物测试
You're just gonna go take a bio quiz.
假装你没有差点被杀死吗
and pretend like you didn't almost get slaughtered?
你也不会放弃猎魔 不是吗
You're not giving up hunting, are you?
当然不会
Hell, no.
艾莉克斯 也许还会有吸血鬼来找你
Alex, other vamps may come for you.
我知道 我会做好准备
I know. And I'll be ready.
等我的生活回归正轨 我也许会继续前行
And when I get my life together, I might be moving on.
艾莉克斯 你不用为了保护我们而离开
Alex, you don't have to leave to protect us.
不是因为这个
That's not why.
我不想面对你们的工作
I can't be around what you all are doing…
和你们猎杀的东西
the things you're fighting.
又要一对二了 你不会有事吧
Are you gonna be all right now that you're outnumbered again?
只要大家都戴避孕套 我们就没问题
Ah, as long as everyone wears a condom, we'll be fine.
这话该做成车尾贴
I want that bumper sticker.